( MARIE WHISPERING )
( REPEATING )
MARIE : I won 't let anyone come between us anymore .
Southern France
I won 't let anyone come between us anymore .
Are they recording ?
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANS )
( SCREECHING )
( ENGINE TURNING OVER )
Help me !
Cigarette .
Light .
I don 't believe the dream I just had .
I was in a forest , running barefoot .
I was hurt , and I was being followed by somebody , and ...
Well , the more I ran , the more I could sense him coming closer .
Who was the guy stalking you ?
It wasn 't a guy . It was me . That 's the weirdest part .
- It was me running after me . - Don 't you ever have normal dreams ?
No .
Being like everyone else is a bore .
We shouldn 't have partied so much . I feel shitty .
Take a rest . I 'll wake you when we get there .
- Real funny . - I 'll drive if you like .
- Like last time ? - Oh , come on , it was late , and I was tired .
- Tired ? More like wasted . - Well , it was your fault for dumping me
for three hours and disappearing with God knows who .
I hope , at least , that he was worth it .
He was unbelievable .
What a slut !
- Asshole ! - Bimbo !
- Bitch ! - Skank !
You 're a pig .
Are there any cool places to go out here in the country ?
I 'm afraid the town hall is about the only place .
Wow , if I had to live here all year round , I think I 'd shoot myself .
Well , it 's just a different lifestyle . Besides , remember ,
we 're here to study , not to party .
( SARÃ  PERCHÃ  TI AMO BLARING ON STEREO )
- We are not deaf , huh ? - Chill out , Marie .
( SIGHS )
( BOTH SINGING IN ITALIAN WITH STEREO )
TOM : Come on , Hendrix .
( EXCLAIMING )
( FIRING TOY GUN )
Tom , stop shouting . Go inside . You 're giving me a headache .
I 'm just waiting for Alex to get here .
She 'll be here by the time you take your bath .
No , I can 't . Alex hasn 't seen the cowboy .
All right , go inside , take your bath , then put the cowboy suit on again .
( ENCOURAGING HENDRIX )
( MAN GRUNTING )
TOM : Come on , Hendrix .
MAN : Come on . Let 's go .
Again . Again . Again . Keep going .
Look at me . Look at me .
( MOANING )
( ENGINE STARTING )
( I BELIEVE PLAYING ON CAR STEREO )
Eyes on the road .
You 've still got some sarcasm , you know .
Are you sure it 's this way ?
ALEX : Of course . Just up ahead . You turn right at the cornfield .
Oh , look , look . There it is . Turn right . Now you go straight for about 4 kilometers .
- MARIE : Wow , easy to get lost . - Nobody uses this road except for tractors .
MARIE : Four kilometers of this , and it 's goodbye , car .
ALEX : You can 't act that way every time a guy tries to talk to you .
- MARIE : I don 't act that way with everyone . - Come on , Marie , it 's always the same story .
- Stop ! - What 's wrong ?
I think I saw someone .
That 's not funny , Alex .
ALEX : I 'm not kidding . I saw someone in the cornfield .
Stop screwing around like that , will you ?
Alex , come back , please .
Alex !
( TURNS OFF ENGINE )
Shit .
Alex .
If this is a joke , I 'll make you regret it .
Alex , where are you ?
Alex ?
Where are you ?
I 'll get you for this , damn it !
This is really not funny .
Alex , cut it out .
Alex ?
( ENGINE STARTING )
Alex !
( SARÃ  PERCHÃ  TI AMO PLAYING ON CAR STEREO )
Stop , bitch . Come back .
Come back !
Come on , I am sick of your little game .
( ALEX LAUGHING )
Damn you . Enough is enough .
ALEX : I could have left you out here , you know .
MARIE : Yeah , very funny .
- You scared the hell out of me . - No .
Go on , laugh your head off . Very funny .
ALEX : Oh , Marie ...
ALEX : Here we are .
All right . ( LAUGHS ) I see why you passed your exams so easily .
You spend all your time here . There is not too much else to do except study .
That 's right . The only real excitement around here is when a train runs through .
FATHER : Take it easy , Hendrix . Easy , boy .
- Hi . - Hello , Dad .
- How are you ? - ( HENDRIX GROWLING )
- Don 't worry , he doesn 't bite . - Are you talking about me or the dog ?
Marie , this is my pop . Pop , Marie .
Nice to meet you .
So nice to see a person and not just a photo of you .
- Photo ? - You know , the one I took in Spain .
- It 's on the fireplace . - ALEX : You 're part of the furniture .
And this is Tom . Hello , cowboy .
- Aren 't you happy to see me ? - FATHER : Of course he 's happy .
He insisted on waiting up all night for you .
And your mother has been worrying the whole day , of course .
Mom always worries for nothing .
- I think she left you something in the oven . - I told her she didn 't have to do that .
Well , she wasn 't sure if you were gonna have time to eat .
Oh , Mother .
I 'll put Tom Thumb to bed , and I 'll show Marie her room .
Right . All right , then .
I still have some work to do . Good night , girls .
- Good night , Pop . - Good night , sir .
Sweet dreams .
- MARIE : So , what was this place before ? - It was an old farm that my father renovated .
There 're lots of them in the area . Most of them are in ruins .
It 's too bad . They 've lived here five years now .
Did they have any problems with neighbors ?
You mean the rednecks ? Yeah .
They first thought my parents were hippies here to make goat cheese ,
but things are fine now . Well , here 's my room . Yeah ?
Okay , follow me .
- ( QUIETLY ) My parents ' room is on the right . - Mmm-hmm .
This is Tom 's room . You 're upstairs in the guest room , okay ?
I 'm just going to put him to bed .
Okay , all tucked in .
- No , no . - No ?
Nighty-night .
MOTHER : Is that you , Alex ?
My mother . I 'll meet you upstairs .
- Hi , Mom . - Is your friend all settled in ?
- Show her where the blankets are . - Okay .
- Clean towels are in the closet . - Don 't worry .
( DOOR CREAKING )
( WIND HOWLING )
( CREAKING )
Your very own bathroom , huh ? The heater 's electric . Do you want it on ?
- No , I can do it if I get cold . - Well , then ,
- what do you think ? - It 's like a doll 's house , very pretty .
( MUSIC TINKLING )
( WHISTLING )
The problem is , he 's got a girlfriend he doesn 't want to split up with .
- Why are you so interested , then ? - Someone who 's taken must be worth it .
I 'm skeptical of single guys .
- Here . Finished ? - Thanks .
I think it 's too easy to be a womanizer when you 're already taken .
Could be right , I guess .
( ALEX SIGHS )
Maybe he doesn 't even like me .
- What 's his girlfriend like ? - She 's Brazilian .
They 've been together three months .
MARIE : A Brazilian ? What , is he into exoticism or something ?
ALEX : Whatever . I need to get a tan , quick .
And I gotta work on my ass . I tell you , that girl is built .
If you do salsa , I 'll go with you .
Go easy on them , all right ? Or they 'll be up all night , chirping .
And you , Marie ?
- Are you going to finally take the plunge ? - Don 't start with that .
- You 're gonna end up alone . - I 'm not a slut like you .
- ( SCOFFS ) You 're so scared . - Well ...
I 'm gonna have a smoke outside . How about you ?
I 'm beat . I 'm going to bed . Don 't be too long .
- I 'll wake you at 9 : 00 . - What 's the game plan ?
- I was thinking international law to start . - Okay .
- Good night , Alex . - Good night .
Hey , Alex ? I 'm glad that I finally met your family .
Come on , Hendrix . Let 's go .
Good night , Hendrix .
( SIGHING )
( WIND HOWLING )
( WOOD CREAKING )
( RUNAWAY GIRL PLAYING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( BARKING )
( SQUAWKING )
( MOANING )
( HENDRIX BARKING )
( DOORBELL RINGING )
( GASPS )
( DOORBELL CONTINUES RINGING )
( HENDRIX BARKING )
FATHER : I 'm coming .
Quiet , Hendrix .
Who is it ?
What do you want ?
( FATHER SCREAMING )
( GROWLING )
( GLASS SHATTERING )
( FATHER GROANING )
( EXCLAIMING IN PAIN )
- What 's going on , Mommy ? - Nothing much . Now go to sleep .
But what 's that noise ?
Tom , did you hear what I said ? I told you to go to sleep .
Daniel ?
Dan ?
( GASPING )
( PANTING )
( MOTHER SCREAMING )
( CLATTERING )
( SCREAMING CONTINUES )
( GRUNTING )
( BLADE SWISHING )
( SNIFFLING )
( GASPING )
( GASPS )
( SHUSHING )
( MARIE QUIVERING )
( ALEX MOANING )
( MAN GRUNTING )
( ALEX SCREAMING )
( GRUNTING )
Shit , the TV plug !
I can 't believe it .
( MUFFLED SCREAMING )
( CHAIN RATTLING )
( MAN GRUNTING )
( PANTING ) No , no ...
( FOOTSTEPS PLODDING )
( HEAVY BREATHING )
( PANTING )
( EXCLAIMS )
( GASPING )
( MAN BREATHING HEAVILY )
( BREATHING RAPIDLY )
( GASPS )
( WEAKLY ) Why ?
( SNIFFLING )
( STATIC )
Oh , shit !
( THUDDING )
( FOOTSTEPS PATTERING )
Alex ?
( ALEX WHIMPERING )
Alex !
( SOBBING )
( GRUNTS )
Hold on .
It won 't come off .
( GRUNTING )
Wait .
TOM : Mommy ! Mommy !
( BOTH GASP )
Mommy ! Mommy !
Mommy !
( ALEX SOBBING )
( PANTING )
( GUNSHOT )
- ( WAILING ) - Try to calm down , Alex .
If he wanted to kill you , he 'd have already have done it .
Now listen to me , Alex . Listen . Listen to me .
Listen to me , for Christ 's sake .
Tell me where I can find a telephone . In the kitchen ?
( WAILS )
In the kitchen ?
Answer me , Alex . Look , I need your help . I can 't do anything alone . I need you .
I 'll be back .
I 'll be back , Alex . I swear .
He mustn 't know anyone else is in the house . Okay ?
I don 't believe it .
( FOOTSTEPS PLODDING )
( CHAIN RATTLING )
( ALEX SCREAMING )
( ALEX SOBBING )
( WHIRRING )
( FIRE CRACKLING )
( MAN BREATHING )
( GRUNTS )
( GLASS SHATTERS )
The phone 's been cut .
- ( SOBBING ) - I 'm gonna get you out of here . I promise .
( ALEX WHIMPERING )
( STATIC CRACKLING )
( POP SONG PLAYING )
( SOBBING )
( WHISPERING ) You have to stay quiet , Alex .
( WAILING )
You 're going to give us away , dummy .
Alex .
Alex , we 're gonna get out of this , I promise you .
Even if we have to fight our way out , we 're gonna make it .
( SHUSHING )
Listen , Alex , those other girls were alone , but there are two of us .
MARIE : It 's gonna work . It 's got to .
( GRUNTING )
Just a little more .
Alex , I got it open .
We 're in a gas station .
This could be our only shot .
The knife .
In case I don 't come back .
- Miss ? - Please call the police .
What ?
Miss !
MAN : Hey , Jimmy !
- How are you ? - Good .
On your own tonight ?
Uh ... Yeah , weekends are slow .
So they left you to mind the store .
I guess .
MAN : This is the ideal place to bring girls .
Don 't tell me it 's never happened .
If I did , my boss would fire me .
( CHUCKLING )
Come on ...
The old rich ladies that drive through ...
Don 't tell me they never ask for your services .
Ain 't that right , Jimmy ?
Yeah , I guess .
How do I look ?
Do they suit me ?
Yeah .
They look good on you .
- They are good protection ? - From what ?
From the sun .
Yeah , they 're sunglasses .
They 're good protection .
How much do I owe you ?
28 ... Are you taking the glasses ?
I don 't think so . But I need some booze .
Can you give me a bottle of J B ?
Do you have Campbell ?
I 'm not supposed to sell alcohol this late .
- Don 't tell the boss , okay ? - I promise .
( YELLING )
CLOSED
What were you looking at , Jimmy ?
What were you looking at ?
( PANTING )
( CLANGING )
( MAN URINATING )
( FLUSHING )
( SIGHING )
( TRUCK ENGINE STARTING )
Fucking come on ! Pick up !
- Come on ! - MAN : State police .
Please help me !
Calm down . What 's happened ?
The Sorals , they have a farm .
I 'm a friend of their daughter 's .
Some guy broke in and he killed them all !
He 's taken Alex in his truck . God knows what he 'll do .
- He axed the gas station guy . - The gas station guy ?
Are you in a gas station ? Which one ?
Hold on . I 'm looking .
I don 't know . I was in his truck . I couldn 't see .
It 's an old rusty truck .
- Did you get the license plate number ? - No , I was inside ! I couldn 't see .
You know how many trucks there are on the road ?
It can 't be fucking hard to spot an old truck at this time of day !
Stay calm and simply tell me where you are .
The bastard 's getting away .
Send a car or Alex doesn 't stand a chance .
I need your location to be able to help you .
If I blow up this fucking place , will you finally see it , asshole ?
Keys ...
( TIRES SCREECHING )
( SOBBING )
( CHUCKLING )
Where are you going , you bastard ?
Fuck ...
Where did he go ?
( CHUCKLING )
( GRUNTING )
( THUNDER RUMBLING )
( GROANING )
( GRUNTING )
( SCREAMING )
( GASPING )
What do you want from Alex ?
She turns you on ?
She turns me on , too .
She turns me on .
( GRUNTING )
( LAUGHING MANIACALLY )
( GROANS )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
( PANTING )
( GRUNTING )
( MAN EXCLAIMS )
( MARIE GRUNTING )
( MARIE SCREAMING )
( GRUNTING )
( PANTING )
( WAILING )
POLICEMAN ON RADIO : All lights are out . The station looks closed .
We 'll take a look anyway .
Fernand , go round the back .
- Be careful . - Yes , sir .
Sir , the back door is locked . We need ...
Call the DA .
( ON RADIO ) This is Fernand .
We got ourselves a homicide .
This is Fernand . We got ourselves a homicide .
Oh , my God !
( SIGHS )
It 's me , Alex . It 's me .
( CHUCKLING )
It 's all over .
( ALEX SOBBING )
( MARIE LAUGHING )
Oh !
There .
Don 't you touch me !
Don 't you touch me , I said !
It 's all over . He 's dead , Alex .
He 's dead . It 's over .
I don 't know what you 're saying .
- He is dead . - Just leave me alone !
- It 's over , Alex . - Get out !
- Alex . - Get out !
It 's over , Alex . I killed him .
( SOBBING )
Alex .
- Please , come down . - Don 't come near me !
Come on , Alex . Come .
It 's all over . Now he can never do anything to you again .
You bitch , you 're crazy . I 'm gonna tear you to shreds !
It 's me . It 's me , Marie , your friend . I 'm on your side .
I killed him , Alex . It 's finished . He 's dead .
You murderer , you murdered my family . God damn it , my family !
There was nothing I could do to save them . There was just you .
Alex .
Everything 's gonna be okay from now on .
Please , Alex , trust me .
Calm down .
( SCREAMING )
( GROANING )
You can 't escape from me , bitch !
( CHAINSAW REVVING )
I 'll take care of you , Alex !
I 'm gonna take care of you , Alex .
( GRUNTING )
Help ! Help me , please .
Please !
She 's not far . Come on ! Come on !
- What 's going on ? - ( SCREAMING )
( ENGINE TURNING OVER )
Hurry !
( YELLING )
( DRIVER EXCLAIMING )
( ENGINE TURNING OVER )
( SCREAMING )
MAN : I 'll rip your head off !
( SCREAMING IN MOCKERY )
You 'd drive a woman crazy . You little slut .
Do you love me ?
You don 't love me , do you ?
- You don 't . - Yes , I do .
Yes , I love you !
Yes , I do love you !
( TURNS OFF CHAINSAW )
( SOBBING )
( GRUNTING )
( MARIE GASPING )
( ALEX SOBBING )
( WHISPERING ) Nobody will come between us , ever ,
ever again .
I won 't let anyone come between us anymore .
I won 't let anyone come between us ...
She can 't see me , right ?